But then
this prick
has the
nerve to
ask where
he can
take the
clients for
lunch.
He didn't
say who
but I
knew they
were coming
to town
so it
wasn't hard
to figure
out.
So I
told him
about a
new restaurant
that is
opening.
It should
be a
nice place
for them
after a
long flight,
the restaurant.
Twin Peaks,
if you
don't know,
it's kinda
like a
hooters rip
off.
After lunch
they came
by the
office and
I made
sure to
say hi.
They were
clearly not
impressed and
their CTO
even made
a comment
that he
wished I
was handling
things because
he didn't
like the
other guy's
style. They
were clearly
uncomfortable with
his
choice in
restaurant and
he had
some glares
for me
as well.
Edit typo.