from subreddit
Petty Revenge.
Take my
credit, lose
your credibility.
I work
in road
in my
company.
I usually
don't get
involved too
much in
deals like
suppliers and
manufacturers.
That's a
different department.
But my
team and
I have
been working
on a
project that
made it
more
necessary for
me to
get involved
in the
finer details
of a
big manufacturing
deal.
We are
wrapping up
the project
and I
found out
that someone
high up
in the
manufacturing
department has
been meeting
with the
other company
without me
and was
going to
basically take
credit
for all
my team's
work. It
isn't a
huge deal
for me
but it
could affect
bonuses for
some of
my
employees. So
today I
talked to
the coo
who told
me that
they recognized
that my
team did
the work
and deserve
credit. But
that it
was going
to be
easier at
this point
to just
let the
other person
handle the
deal. I
was okay
with this
because we
got the
credit but
it was
a load
off my
plate and
I have
other things
to do.